# LUTFIA AISYA

### FRONTEND DEVELOPER



Amsterdam

aisya.lutfia@gmail.com

+31687937940

in <u>@aisyafia</u> 🗗

@aisyafia 🗗

#### **PROFILE**

I am an adaptable and curious developer. Backed with 5+ years experience in research, business strategy and project management. I am not shy to ask questions, or do some public speaking.

I am creative, resilient, smart and I enjoy being a part of international and intergenerational environments.

I switched career to web development because I am passionate about creating impact through tech solutions.

#### TECH STACKS

JavaScript Typescript Vue React Tailwind Nextjs Redux Bootstrap Axios Git & Github HTML/CSS Node.js SASS Cypress Material UI PostgreSQL Sequelize Figma

#### LANGUAGES

Indonesian - Native
English - Professional/Bilingual
Dutch - Early intermediate (A2 - B1)

#### **WORK EXPERIENCES**

### Frontend Developer | April 2024 - present | Amsterdam, NL

Developing features and functionality as part of SaaS solution utilizing Vue, TypeScript, and Tailwind

- Develop new features across multiple applications in company's suite
- Bug investigation and fixes
- Implement Design Systems: from Figma design into reusable components
- Collaboration in teams within Agile development environments
- Code reviews and version control
- Learn and apply coding standards and best practices through internal guild

## Front End Web Developer Intern | September 2023 - March 2024 | Amsterdam, NL NLC - The European Healthtech Venture Builder

Designed, created, and styled the front-end part of internal applications. Tech tools: Figma, Spring Boot (Java, NodeJS), HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, SASS, Git

Warehouse Supervisor | January - October 2022 | Amsterdam, NL Gorillas | On-demand grocery delivery service

Key responsibilities: small-scale performance management, administration and customer service. Tech tools: Quinyx, Zenput, Slack, in-house Dashboard

Editor | August - September 2020 | Delft, NL
GIZ Brussels Office | German Social-Development Agency

Freelance editorial work on policy papers. Focus area: climate change and energy policy in Indonesia

**Business Development Lead** | January 2018 - January 2020 | **Jakarta, ID TaniFund** | A financial technology company focusing on crowdfunding

- Promoted from Business Process Improvement specialist
- Initiated and supervised the Project Management team
- Created standardized process for loan application and approval
- Developed strategies for user retention and acquisition

Sourcing Encodage | October 2016 - August 2017 | Brussles, BE Bureau van Dijk - A Moody's Analytics

Key responsibilities: research and administration

Researcher | January 2014 - August 2015 | Jakarta, ID Microfinance Innovation Center for Resources and Alternatives

#### **EDUCATION**

Full-Stack Development | October 2022 - January 2023 | Codaisseur

10 intensive weeks where I learnt and applied modern technologies from back-end to front-end to build full-stack web. Scored 90% in the final assessment.

MSc in Development Studies | 2015 - 2017 | University Antwerp, Belgium

The Institute of Development Policy (IOB) is a multidisciplinary faculty dedicated in academic research and education to contribute to economic, political and social aspects of development policies. Thesis theme: microfinance and climate change.

BA in Banking and Finance | 2008 - 2012 | Indonesia Banking School, Indonesia

Indonesia Banking School (IBS), established in 2004, is a premier higher education institution in Jakarta specializing in finance and business education with a strong emphasis on digital technology.